ehealthme.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy policy of eHealthMe - real world drug outcomes

## Privacy Policy

eHealthMe.com ("eHealthMe") understands how important the privacy of personal information is to our users. This Privacy Policy will tell you what information we collect about you and about your use of eHealthMe and its services. It will explain the choices you have about how your personal information is used and how we protect that information. We urge you to read this Privacy Policy carefully.

**Part 1: About This Privacy Policy and Using Our Site and Tools**

**Part 2: Non-Personal Information We Collect About You**

**Part 3: Personally Identifiable Information We Collect About You and Third Parties**

**Part 4: Disclosure of Your Information**

**Part 5: How eHealthMe Handles Privacy and Security Internally**

**Part 6: Third Party Advertisers**

**Part 7: Changes to this Privacy Policy**

**Part 8: Glossary**

**_Part 1: About This Privacy Policy and Using Our Site and Tools_**

This Privacy Policy applies to the eHealthMe web site. 

The eHealthMe web site contains links to other sites. Once you enter another Web site (whether through a service, or content link), be aware that eHealthMe is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to look for and review the privacy statements of each and every Web site that you visit through a link on eHealthMe. 

We hope that reading our Privacy Policy gives you a clear idea of how we manage information about you. Throughout our Privacy Policy, we have underlined various terms and hot-linked them to our Glossary or to the corresponding Section within the Privacy Policy to help you better understand their meaning. 

Functionality of eHealthMe can be used without registration. If you use our Web site, the only information we collect will be Non-Personal Information through email address and the use of Cookies. Depending on the tool or service you have selected, we may also collect Personal Health Information. You are responsible for ensuring the accuracy of the Personally Identifiable Information and Personal Health Information you submit to eHealthMe. Inaccurate information will affect the information you receive when using our site and tools and our ability to contact you as described in this Privacy Policy. 

**_Part 2: Non-Personal Information We Collect About You_**

We collect Non-Personal Information about your use of our Web site. 

**Cookies**

We collect Non-Personal Information about your use of our Web site through the use of Cookies. Every computer accesses eHealthMe web site is assigned a different Cookie by eHealthMe. The information collected by Cookies allows us to statistically monitor how many people are using our Web site. 

Most browser software can be set to reject all Cookies. Most browsers offer instructions on how to reset the browser to reject Cookies in the "Help" section of the toolbar. If you reject our Cookies, certain of the functions and conveniences of our Web site may not work properly but you do not have to accept our Cookies in order to productively use our site. We do not link Non-Personal Information from Cookies to Personally Identifiable Information without your permission and do not use Cookies to collect or store Personal Health Information about you. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.eHealthMe.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any sites connected with eHealthMe.

**Log Files**

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

**_Part 3: Personally Identifiable Information We Collect About You and Third Parties_**

We collect Personally Identifiable Information that you provide to us when you check drug interactions and adverse effects. We use the Personally Identifiable Information that you provide to respond to your questions, send you emails about Web site maintenance and updates, and inform you of significant changes to this Privacy Policy. 

Your email is used to receive links to report results, respond to your inquiries, and notify you of service related updates. You may not opt-out of receiving any of these service related communications that are not promotional in nature. 

**Children**

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. Neither eHealthMe nor any of its services are designed or intended to attract children under the age of 13. We do not collect Personally Identifiable Information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13. 

**_Part 4: Disclosure of Your Information_**

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy or as specifically agreed to by you, eHealthMe will not disclose any Personally Identifiable or Personal Health Information it gathers from you on our website. We may only release Personally Identifiable or Personal Health Information to third parties: (1) to comply with valid legal requirements such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order; or (2) in special cases, such as in response to a physical threat to you or others, to protect property or defend or assert legal rights. In the event that we are legally compelled to disclose your Personally Identifiable or Personal Health Information to a third party, we will attempt to notify you unless doing so would violate the law or court order. In addition, we may disclose Personal Information as described below. 

**Disclosure Re Linked Sites**

For your convenience there are links to Third Party Web sites operated by companies that are not affiliated with the eHealthMe web site and that do not have contracts to provide content or services through the eHealthMe web site. These links may be found referenced within content, or placed beside the names or logos of sponsors. eHealthMe does not disclose your Personal Information to these Third Party Websites without obtaining your consent. eHealthMe does not endorse and is not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites and the personal information collected there is governed by these third parties' privacy practices. If you choose to link to one of these Third Party Web sites, you should review the privacy policy posted on this other website to understand how that Third Party Web site collects and uses your Personally Identifiable Information 

**_Part 5: How eHealthMe Handles Privacy and Security Internally_**

Listed below are some of the security procedures that eHealthMe uses to protect your privacy: 

  * Requires both a personal username (log-in name) and a password in order for users to access their Personally Identifiable Information or Personal Health Information. 
  * No Personally Identifiable Information is disclosed on eHealthMe website.
  * Closely monitors the limited number of eHealthMe employees who have potential access to your Personally Identifiable Information. 
  * Requires all eHealthMe employees to abide by our Privacy Policy and to be subject to disciplinary action if they violate it. 
  * Backs-up our systems to protect the integrity of your Personally Identifiable and Personal Health Information. 

Despite eHealthMe's efforts to protect your Personally Identifiable Information and Personal Health Information, there is always some risk that an unauthorized third party may find a way around our security systems or that transmissions of your information over the Internet may be intercepted. 

**_Part 6: Third Party Advertisers_**

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by third party ad servers. We share Web site usage information about users with reputable third parties Google, Amazon, among others, for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on this site.

These third party ad servers use cookies and/or Web beacons on this site, which allow it to recognize a user's cookie when a user visits this site. The information that these third party ad servers collect and share through this technology is not personally identifiable. 

Google, one of our third-party advertisers, may add a cookie to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences and your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. You can choose to opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**_Part 7: Changes to this Privacy Policy_**

Personally Identifiable Information - We will inform you if a material change to the Privacy Policy, which means a change that expands the permissible uses or disclosures of Personally Identifiable Information allowed by the prior version of the Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently.  If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a prominent notice on our home page.

Your continued use of the eHealthMe web site after giving you notice and choice (if applicable when related to a material change) will indicate acceptance of the changes. You may of course choose to Opt-out of continuing to use the eHealthMe web site. Please exit the site immediately if you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy or any revised policy. 

Personal Health Information - We will inform you if a material change in the Privacy Policy is made that involves the use of your Personal Health Information, and your express Opt-in authorization will be requested. eHealthMe reserves the right to discontinue or limit functionality in all its services and products. 

Non-Significant Changes. eHealthMe may make non-significant changes to the Privacy Policy that do no affect Personally Identifiable Information or Personal Health Information. For these instances, eHealthMeLat may not notify you of such non-significant changes. 

If you have questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

support@eHealthMe.com

**_Part 8: Glossary_**

**browser:** Short for web browser, a browser is a software application used to locate and display web (Internet) pages. The most popular browsers are AOL, FireFox, Microsoft Internet Explorer, and Netscape Navigator. In addition, most modern browsers can present multimedia information, including sound and video, though they require plug-ins for some formats. 

**cache (also called cache memory):** Once your Web browser accesses a web page, it references that page and the graphics on it within your computer's "cache" (or more simply, your computer takes a "snapshot" of every page you visit and stores it in the "cache".) The next time you visit that same page, your download time will be quicker as the images and much of the page is already available on your computer for your browser to reference instantly instead of waiting for the page and images to download again. 

**Click Stream Information:** A record of all the pages you have visited during your visit to a particular Web site or the services you accessed from the site or from an email. Click Stream Information is associated with your browser and not with you personally. It records the archives of your browser. 

**Cookie:** A small data file that is stored on the hard drive of the computer you use to view a Web site. Cookies are placed by that site or by a third party with a presence on the site, and are accessible only by the party or site that placed the Cookie (i.e. a Cookie placed on your computer by eHealthMe isn't accessed by any other site you visit but a Cookie placed on your computer by a third party may be accessed by any site on which that same party has a presence). Cookies can contain pieces of Personally Identifiable Information (PII). These Cookies often are used to make the site easier to use. 

**Non-Personal Information:** Information that is not traceable back to any individual and cannot be used to identify an individual. For example, Click Stream Information is Non-Personal Information, as is information such as gender, age, city and state when not linked with other Personally Identifiable Information. 

**Opt-In:** Means you are actively indicating your preference to participate in a program, email, feature, tool, or enhancement on a Web site. Typically, if you "Opt-in" you must provide certain information, usually Personally Identifiable Information, to the Web site or otherwise actively indicate your choice or preference to participate in the Web site program. 

**Opt-Out:** Means that if you do not take some action you are indicating your preference to participate in a program, email, feature, tool or enhancement on a Web site. 

**Personal Health Information (PHI):** When your Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is combined with known health characteristics. For example, if you indicated that you have a certain disease or condition, when that information is combined with your PII, it becomes Personal Health Information. 

**Personally Identifiable Information (PII)** (also called Personal Information): Information that can be traced back to an individual (contrast with Non-Personal Information and Aggregate Information). Examples of PII include your name, home address, telephone number, email address, and Social Security number. eHealthMe does not collect Social Security number.

If other pieces of information are linked to PII, they also become PII. For example, if you use a nickname to chat online and give out your real name while chatting, your nickname becomes PII when linked with other PII. 

**server:** A computer that provides services to other computers. A "web server" stores web site files and "serves" them to people who request them. 

**virus:** A program or piece of code that is loaded onto your computer without your knowledge and runs against your wishes. Viruses can also "replicate" themselves by copying their code to other computers. All computer viruses are manmade. A simple virus that can make a copy of itself over and over again is relatively easy to produce. Even such a simple virus is dangerous because it will quickly use all available memory and bring the system to a halt. An even more dangerous type of virus is one capable of transmitting itself across networks and bypassing security systems. 

**web beacons (also often referenced as "clear GIFs", "web bugs", "1-by-1 GIFs", "Single-Pixel GIFs", "1 x 1 Pixels", or "clear Pixels"):** Tiny graphic image files, imbedded in a web page in GIF, jpeg or HTML format, typically used to monitor activity on a web page and send back to its home server (which can belong to the host site, a network advertiser or some other third party) information from your browser, such as the IP address, the URL of the page on which the beacon is located, the type browser that is accessing the site and the ID number of any Cookies on your computer previously placed by that server. Web Beacons can also be used to place a Cookie on your computer.

Last modified: April 07, 2009
